He's too young.
And he's your employee.
What on earth are you thinking?
You guys are seriously dating, right?
- Right?
- What do you mean, "right"?
What else?
What's the deal with that kid?
He's super cute.
Right? Right?
It was love at first sight for me.
Even so, I still worry.
I know very well.
My next ten years
and Ai-chan's next ten years.
The speed and weight of time passing
are completely different.
That goes without saying.
He still has a long road ahead of him.
Yeah.
It's not like the time I have left.
Collapsing made me
realize that all over again.
But you don't want to let go just yet?
Until Ai-chan shakes me off,
I'll hold on to him tightly.
That's gross.
What do you mean, "shakes me off"?
- So gross.
- Don't say it twice.
Whatever.
I'll head home for today.
You can just see me off here.
That kid is still waiting for you, right?
See ya.
I just can't let go.
"Are the Sexy Buttocks Not Good?"
(Episode 9)
Hey.
I love you so much.
Did your sister say anything to you?
No.
Should we go on a date?
Wow, it's so pretty.
What's with that look?
Nothing.
Come to think of it,
we haven't really been on a proper date.
We can just go on more dates from now on.
Hold this for a sec. Let's take a picture.
How is it?
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Come on, smile.
Looks good.
What kind of date do you want?
Going to an aquarium or watching a movie.
What are you doing?
So cute.
I already knew that.
I haven't said it enough.
Should I shout it out right here?
- So cute!
- Stop it!
Someone will call the cops.
By the way.
About earlier.
Earlier?
(Earlier)
(I'm sorry I couldn't say we're dating.)
Ai-chan.
(No.)
(It's my fault for not being able to say
we're in a relationship.)
Did you not like it?
That I told my sister
you're my boyfriend.
It's fine.
It'd be weird to hide
it at this point anyway.
(Huh!)
(Then why couldn't I say it?)
For a date, going to a hot
spring would be nice too.
You don't have to
figure it all out at once.
Are you by any chance
hiding something bad again?
No, no.
But that day will come eventually.
You really are thinking about weird things.
Eventually isn't right now.
We still have so many things
we can do together in the future.
Until we run out of things to do,
whether it's a hot spring or whatever,
I'll go with you.
However,
it's pretty sexy, right?
Ai-chan at a hot spring
would definitely be sexy.
Oh boy.
In a private bath.
Don't go into dirty old man mode.
So sexy.
Sexy.
So,
are you moving out of here?
I haven't decided yet.
It's just that,
if I move out,
I'll have to tell my parents.
But when I think about
introducing him to my family,
I'm not confident I can introduce him
the way Okumi-san did.
Inferiority complex?
Guilt?
- That's the one.
- So annoying.
Huh?
The old guy didn't ask you to
introduce him to your parents.
You're just stressing
yourself out over nothing.
But Okumi-san introduced me to his sister
as his boyfriend.
Yet I...
So you're going to tell your parents you're
dating a guy, who's not only an older man,
but also the boss of your company?
Even if things are going well now,
who knows if you'll stay together forever.
The future, huh.
Introducing him to your parents...
I feel like that's the final hurdle.
The future.
I thought I'd always be
with Okumi-san in the future too.
I see.
When he becomes an old man,
I have to be the one by his side.
And I haven't really thought
about what happens after that.
As for introducing him to my parents...
Didn't you want to keep
it a secret from them?
I don't think I want to hide it.
Though I'm not entirely sure myself.
I want my parents to meet Okumi-san.
I want to properly talk to
them about the person I love.
These feelings aren't a lie.
You're so conflicted,
yet surprisingly resolute.
Thanks for listening to me.
Whether to let my parents know
or how to introduce our relationship,
none of that matters.
What matters is what I want to do.
And what I want to do right now is...
Welcome back.
Ai-chan.
I want to do it.
Huh?
Even if I can't see the future,
even if I'm not fully prepared for it,
I want to be with this person forever.
Am I being too greedy?
What's wrong?
I want all of Okumi-san.
Don't you already have it?
Wait.
Today, I want to make Okumi-san feel it.
I want to be with this person.
I'm planning to move out of my apartment.
Huh?
Are you serious?
You asked knowing I'd turn down
living together, right?
No.
You actually want to live together, but you're
wondering if it's okay to make me go that far.
- Right?
- When did you learn to read minds?
I didn't.
I pretty much know
what the person I love is thinking.
Does the person you love mean me?
Who else could it be?
Ai-chan.
I...
I love Okumi-san.
- Ouch.
- Sorry, sorry.
I guess I was too hasty after all.
No.
I'm really happy.
But it was so sudden, it startled me.
Because I realized my own feelings.
I have to contact my parents and tell them
I'm moving out of my apartment.
Right now? So suddenly?
Mom, I'm doing great.
Um,
there's someone I want to live with.
(Preview for the Final Episode)
He's my boyfriend.
Who would hand our Ai-chan over
to a man like this?
I want to cherish Okumi-san properly.
Don't go anywhere.
I'm right by your side.
I'm not going anywhere.